Hi
I don't think that
I don't know who were the lifeless section guy. I mean whatever he talked about a lot of stuff. Maybe I should have been awake
Monitoring I should have I don't know if he talked about something inappropriate or something you guys just gather up
Hi guys, good morning
Good afternoon
Yeah
Hi
Yeah, something happened last night. I guess it was
JT
Now we'll talk to you several times like I'm like city never, you know, you're not supposed to put up
Pictures of other people. I'm supposed to harass people in the chat. They're just chatting
and then
He put up some of that and then he's like oh report this bitch and then he put it's up animal animal
I'm just a little
Luckily that thing happened
You know, I mean, why did you do that? I asked you not to do that, you know, you know, you know, I wasn't here, you know
You want to try to protect the show, right?
Why would you do that?
I'll let you back on for you. This is why this is why you weren't made mod. It's why you weren't
You know
You were keep on panel sometimes. It's like the same stuff and you're doing the same stuff
You were played dumb and they oh, I didn't that wasn't this. No, this was this. Oh, it's not cool. I
Asked you not to do it
But I think it's stressful when I ask people
Hey, you know
You don't have to like my shirt. I don't know of course
Of course they're gonna
After me, but no
Stop
I mean, I didn't I didn't know what I was looking at. I didn't see the picture of he was putting up somebody's picture
I know that that's probably them
God he was kind of there like laughing a lot. I don't think he was really doing it, but
Yeah, it's pretty disgusting
I just want to know how should JT be dealt with for that like
The everyone's everyone's upset
Yeah, I mean I was I get uh, I mean it was just was like it lasted a second, you know, it was I didn't know what I was looking at
But why would you put stuff like that up on my show?
You know, but yeah, it was up with that bother
I mean the person I
What game is it? What game is it? There is no game. My show is fine. I'm just telling you, I have people telling me things and flipping things for me.
But anyway, not cool.
I don't know. Is there a reason for it?
Hey, nobody everybody in chat. Well, you know, I
Just want to address that I know who's bothering you Jamie
I don't remember if I like what happened, I don't remember if I forgot to end my stream or I forgot to or I just
I fell asleep and I know you guys did you have this like oh I
have a vape and it just knocked me out I just stuck up on me I'm sorry guys
Maybe cash
No, it's fun last night, I don't know
People people people people to Jack
Hi, babe
We had some good some interesting shows yesterday. Everything was good yesterday.
Hey Vicky
Well, I'm sorry guys
Thank you, I know that really Nancy and Paige were trying to wake me up, you know fortunately I
Have a deep sleeper I
Feel bad
I'm sorry guys, I mean leave you alone. I know it scares you
You believe it three on the panel we're trying to get my channel taken down
Unsuccessful
And that form over to
Yeah
Let me check make sure my channel is okay
My channel is fine. Hey, I also got guys two thousand five hundred fifty five subscribers. Wow. It's awesome
But it seems like it's kind of slow you have a card sure it's a little bit slow
Okay
You got an eight of wands so it's when I knew it was coming in fast for you
Maybe if you've been waiting for this news for a long time, maybe build it too slow
Like you're not getting answered fast enough. It's coming the answers coming
It'll come fast when it comes in
It says eight of wands
Shows that lots of things in your life are changing very quickly. You're heading into a fast-paced time
Don't get bogged down in the details instead. Try to go with the new flow use momentum to power your creativity
inspiration everywhere
You like that
And very welcome
Yeah
I need to raise your demand yeah, cuz it's like I know I was like I wish people wouldn't be trying to take that much my channel
No purpose
But then again
If they want they would you know, I can't believe I left them alone the panel, but they
You know
I'm okay.
Good morning guys
You wanna come up panel good morning. I don't know
Thank you, sassy
What am I gonna do about the people trying to destroy my channel well this is this report to me who they are I mean is but JT
Was God trying to I don't know was that lepo section guy trying to I don't know
He was talking about some controversial stuff
You know how much can be done except I just have to be here. I just can't
Can't let people run the show anymore
Sebastian yeah, I mean if they yeah, was he okay? I mean, I don't know. I like I woke up
He was still talking I woke up and then I came back. He was gone. I turned up the strip
I mean I was I didn't hear him say anything bad like that bad
It's a group of them
Okay
You know, I was just, guys, you, if I, if you see stuff that I, that I miss, here's Dougie.
Um, how you doing?
Good morning. I'm doing okay. How are you?
I'm okay. Let me turn the volume up. I can't hear you. Okay.
That's better.
It's just that...
So, uh, you were, you were up very late last night and fell asleep, right?
Yeah.
And then this morning I got a there's an email and says hey, hey, well look what JT was doing and
Then a JT like with during the show your first year putting up somebody's
Somebody's photo somebody else. I think they were in the chat, too
And then he put up some kind of beastiality some kind of like a beastiality in there. I heard all of that
Yeah, now you had you left people on your on your panel when you fell asleep, right? Yeah
That's usually not a good plan. Yeah
Sorry, I'm responding to a text message. Well, luckily I look at my phone. See my phone. Yeah
Old flip phone
Not too old, but yeah
It's only like two or three years old. It's not that old. Yeah, it's cool
I uh, I was able to delete it. I also you know, the video was not flagged or anything. It was just like a
You know my friend from burger boys
Hi tap water. I'm not sure I've met tap water, but nice to
Tap water is a friend of mine a young lady
Hello vicki
Um, so you fell asleep people on your panel and then they fucked around I was reading
I was reading people. I was reading what people were talking about at a different chat site earlier today
They're talking about that. Yes
They're kind of a
Celebratory way or what were they trying to where they kind of like as if they've done something fantastic kind of
or fun or in any way funny, I guess. Right? Okay. They did use the word
Vcality and they did mention people by name like you did.
Well, you know, luckily, you know, so then I went to those divine divine intervention with
you know, like with Ilya, you know, his camera turning off accidentally and I don't know.
So I just have to I don't know if I can't trust them off, but I'm not there
I can't I don't know if I can even trust them when I'm on there because sometimes I
Have had the opposite thing happen. I've had people sitting on my panel fall asleep
Person I'll read mod you person because person does program my nightbot and stuff. Yeah, I trust you to do that
For a person is
Person is a good man. It's just a person. I am I'm not everybody. I know you're not
I'm not really not worried like one way or the other
like
The nice thing about what I like about being a mod and I don't ever like if it's not my channel
I don't discipline anybody unless the host asked me to then I well
That's my job. But what I do as a mod is I look at everybody's channel
And then I look and see if they have stuff if people have comments on their stuff. I can go to those people's channels also
Yep, you know what I mean?
I can look and look and look and that was that
That helps me get subscribers because people who I see that I like I'll sub to them and leave them a note
Sometimes they sub back, you know, yeah
And then again and their audience can see you know, you're posting there too your comments you get stuff, so
Yeah, so yes, and yeah, my show's really been like, you know picking back up yesterday
I had over a hundred people in the chat at one point
There I wasn't it wasn't personal person. It was just a person a person does the
It doesn't work with the nightbot and stuff, you know, so I'll be in the minds of that. I
Yeah
So but yeah, so everything's okay. Everything's okay. But yeah, that's you know, I think you guys really if it wasn't for people like watching
After me, I probably would I probably might even let the email this morning that alerted you. You didn't get anything
Did you know no?
They'll come up and do something that they know can get you in trouble with YouTube whether it's exposed
And then if you don't shut your stream down and throw it out, they'll go to YouTube and report you. Yeah, right?
So then YouTube comes right over and has a look
Yeah, so when shit like that happens and it's happened to me. I've been porn bomb, you know a handful of times maybe six
I don't know and and what you have to do is you have to throw the stream out
Don't even leave it on your channel. Yeah
You're not even allowed to put it back there and hold it. You know what I mean? Yeah. Oh
Yeah, he was talking about that stuff. Oh my gosh black RG. Yeah, I deleted it had like some kind of like it has some kind of like
I'm not even going to mention the topic, but it had some kind of like message about
Oh, this will be discussed in the video is giving the correct definition of whatever the yeah
There's just some kind of weird thing. I don't know what he was talking about. But yeah, that was my fault. Wow guys
You know, I have to make sure to shut down the stream. It's not worth it. It's like, you know, and it's a wake-up call
You know, I've done it a handful of times or more. You know, this is very responsible and
So I think I was you know, the thing I think it was crisis averted. I think you know
It's uh, I think there was no warning. No
Sebastian by Sebastian. So look, you know, flow key like Sebastian who did it was talking about it was JT
JT, I saw them, you know, he put up one's photo which I've asked him not to do to put anybody's photo up in
an harassing way and then he put up
He said oh report this bitch or something like that and then he put up some kind of
So watching it open together. Yeah, so I I did I couldn't even recognize what it was. That's why I don't know
It was horse. I just I couldn't even I didn't know what I was looking at. It was a little
Small graphic or something like that
It's good not to get all worked up about that shit because it just feeds them and they wanted
You know keep doing it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, this is one of the know
Like, you know, well God God I didn't
Say anything wrong, you know, he was kind of like maybe laughing along with it, but it was really JT that
Forbidden stuff. Yeah
You know, and I drew a picture of him and stuff, you know, I was you know tried to
It'll be nice and have him on the show. I don't know. I've given him chances that I
No, I give everybody every chance I can I've had people
You know really fuck me over up on my channel, and I still let them come in the chat and talk and
You know some people I don't let on my panel anymore, but I have
There's very few people you know they have to earn that spot which did not be let up. You know what I mean?
They have to earn that
Yeah, it's hard cuz I do like people but it's like it's it's like I can't like it's hard to I know you know
I know I know my friends are pretty much, but you know, it's like every people
That are just actively trying to fuck with me. It's not fun. The black heart. He says this is W. Doug black heart G
He's also a he's a he's a content creator. He has a channel. I think he has panels
Let's have a look. I don't know that I have you banned on my channel, buddy
I'm pretty sure I timed you out but I don't know that you're banned. Let me look at your account a minute
Yeah, nobody's described it is March 23rd 2024. Yeah, I remember that I timed you out
By all means, uh, nobody but I don't think I banned you
I just don't think that's the case
Yeah
I'll look into it and if I do have you on the list, I'll do something
But if you are banned it's because you did something fucked up and earned it. I will say that
Nobody did you do I know nobody for you, you know, he's been here for a while and he's always a
Good of my chat there, but I'm not sure. Did you something bad in W does yet? Yeah, I'm talking about nobody
Yeah, nobody coming being a good civilian
Sometimes that's inappropriate you better read my chat guidelines
right
Some people think talking shit about another person is being a good civilian
But that violates my get my chat guidelines. So that that could be an issue. Nobody. I'm sorry. I'll start talking to them
I don't want to be shit. He's just fucking around. Yeah, I know they're fucking around anyway. Yeah
Okay, they're even restrict that Argentinian military
Yeah, thank you, Tiffany. Yeah, I thought they're bothering you. Yeah, I just leave the stream and
I'm sorry. I'm sorry if they were harassing. I saw
Were they harassing you? I'm not
Thank you for no, but she told miss quick to go skip a rope
But this was a new thing. Oh, well, he does me. Oh, you're you're nobody's hearing more your channels falling off
I just like you know, this says they might think there's and then the yesterday you said it
There's ten people the chat and then that same stream. There's like a hundred people the chat later
So, you know, they were they don't they don't talk with there's like a hundred people in the chat. It is the
It's come in the beginning and say oh nobody's here anymore. I'm trying to mess with me
Hey, look at number one JC Wasey's number one of the chat person is number two
We had sassy scarlet number three and have you seen this like the ratings and this
The new thing that has popped in my in my chat said this rating system. I'm seeing it
I don't know what that means. I don't know what that's about. I'm not monetized
So it doesn't happen in my place. Yeah, right. So I don't know what that what that's all about
But I go to people's chats and sometimes I'm like first thing I say and I'm like I'm number two and I'm like what did I do?
I mean, it's like what that is some people have 25 points some people have 50 points and some people have 75 points and that you know
But I don't know how you earn points if anyone didn't want to know anything about it like
Like I don't know how I get points because I see a
Like I've got you know, it's not a Lisa's channel
I see our leases for like a couple weeks now a few weeks now, but it's appeared on mine. And so I don't know
how you build up how you build up points or anything so let me know if you have any tips about
some chats or showing people's instead of the display name it shows people's ads as a
display name yeah I guess they're experimenting with some stuff right now I don't need to they're
always experimenting with some new stuff you know you just we're able to get the comments on the
screen through stream you already see other comments come on the screen right there they come
Has an extreme your future? Yes. Yes, it was nobody. I noticed that this morning at a couple of different chat rooms
I went to it was showing the
The ad address rather than the name. That's a YouTube glitch. I assume. I don't know what else that could be
But it could fuck somebody up if they've been changing their name a lot
Because if you look at their old chat, you know, you you could figure out, you know, that that could fuck somebody up
You can change your name every couple weeks. I guess, you know, I've been on I've been under as much as the alias
Even my alias accounts, I usually reveal who I haven't blocked me. So I'm actually blocked her
Sunday astonishing number of
chat rooms and
You know people get mad at me for having them out. I'm like, oh my gosh
Well, I'm blocked and so many places where I can make really never go even a multiple accounts in some places
Browser access to reveal your channel
Person I've got I've got an app that I can go to everybody's channel. I just go over and go to your channel right now
right
And it's just it's called go to channel
November 15th, 2021
person
Yeah, right I'm right at your channel because I have the I have this app
It's called
Go-to-channel it's called go-to-channel
You download that thing and you can go to anybody's channel at any time as long as you have it on you turn it
You could turn it on and off
Right
You're out of
HK yeah, we've been great. Great number of people very 43 people on chat this afternoon. Yeah, I just woke up
Kind of with tricks
Yeah, so
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna be more careful guys and
If you guys thank you so much for guys for like, you know, I'm just for people
That will send me full full video clips of what what happened exactly what happened and you know really helped me
You know see I don't really watch back shows, you know, I would I would not listen to back to last night, you know
Good morning fellas. How are you?
Doing good
You look like the guy from up remember
Yeah, don't don't don't mistake me for Doug D. That's somebody
Know that you guys are different people
Yeah
Today after last night was pretty exciting wasn't it what's going on?
Yeah, that's going on it was I can't believe I fell asleep though. I and uh, you know
It's like you're like the king for fall asleep on your panels or leaving your panel and going to another panel
Who is your grandpa site what the fuck going on?
It's awesome guy
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
No idea.
Hello.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
We can hear you.
Can you hear us?
What's up?
No.
You got your uncle up here?
Well, who is your uncle?
Your brother?
What's up, Eldo?
And I'm not trying.
Oh, that's good.
Hello, Samir.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
I'm not trying.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah. Well, so, you know, Paige,
you know, so this is Doug.
Yeah, I know Prairie Page. We
spoke in the chat. I might have
been on the panel with it once,
but I don't I'm not sure I do
see you on the panel all the
time. What are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
Okay, he's having a hard time
hearing, I guess.
Canada's good. It's smoky and kind of like overcast-y, so the golf course won't be busy
But then again, if it's not too hot people also like to golf then as well
So we'll see because it pissed yesterday
It was thunderstorming the power went out and everything and there was still people out on the golf course
I was like fuck. Yeah
Go hard
Yeah, it's the work today. Are you working today or is there a day and then I work tomorrow and then I don't work Sunday
But I work almost every day. I think I've only had like two days off since I started. Oh
Wow, yeah, yeah working hard. That's great. Well, someone's got to pay these fucking bills and it sure the fuck is definitely me
Yeah, so
Do you do um, wait, what do you do really? I mean for for you is your are you full-time streamer like me or
Yeah, no
Okay
YouTube, I'm not monetized and I'm just really socializing I've met people I have a lot of friends and like I've told you
Australia and India and Holland and England and Germany people all over the world. It's fun to meet
I'm a retired union. I work in New York City. Thank you
Wow
I mean I got in the iron work his union in 1986. I was like 21 years old
So, working with iron, that sounds kind of ever-dangerous.
Well, we install steel, high-rises, bridges, we did, you know, we do subway work and underground
work too.
Oh, wow.
That's cool.
That's what I did.
Wow.
Thank you for your services.
Well, I was just, you know, it's...
Yeah.
So much that it didn't work, right? And it pays why and it gives good benefits and every other thing. So, yeah
Service did he provide?
Yeah, iron worker providing just everything that needs iron like the whole city
It's not just structural steel we do rebar we do siding, you know, we hang the siding iron work is a pretty broad field in fact
You know nowadays all the buildings are clad with siding the big panels. Yeah, I remember the crane, right? We do that, too. I
Did not liberate Kuwait 90 in 91
I was never in the service
Thanks for the comment page. I'm not a veteran
Are you no
Ain't there a Dougie D in chat
No
That's not me
I was gonna say good morning to everybody. Hey, Jamie. Hey punchy. Nobody got person scum a
Pija Darrell, I don't know you Darrell, but hello
um, what else
Jamie already said you tb
Think that's about it. Oh easy's here. What's up, Jonathan? Sam?
J-Dog. A lot of people here this morning. Whole gang's here. Good morning, family.
Afternoon, I guess. Afternoon, isn't it now?
Hey, Traveling Gypsy's in the chat. Hey, Traveling Gypsy. Hey, Gypsy. Glamé, thank you.
Yeah, everyone was talking about crowns. I was like, what is everyone talking about crowns?
Are they playing game of thrones? I was so confused. I was like, I don't understand who we're talking about because it was
I have to look at my phone and then they can see like there's crowns next to people's names like the top three people in chat
I don't know. It's a really interesting feature
Fancy last night or something I thought because these like the green names are new too, but anyway, so I thought you were doing it
Oh yeah, well it's a green name, those are the members and so yeah, there's been a lot
of memberships donated and like a lot of people, you know, I donated a few and then a bunch
of people donated multiple memberships and you know, I think everybody who were donating
When I get paid, I'll do, I'll do my part as well.
Donating membership, donating membership is good.
I've never bought a membership for myself on someone's channel,
but I've donated on a few different channels.
And what happens when you start to donate memberships,
is you start to receive donated memberships.
Yeah, what goes around comes around kind of thing, yeah.
Because I didn't buy a membership on Sykes channel,
but I'm a member, why?
Somebody donated memberships and I got,
why was my name on the list?
Because I donate memberships on this channel and others I've donated the memberships here and I've donated them at a few
I don't I don't think that's true because I'm top donator buddy, and I haven't received a furry membership
Random it is random. So you know, but you know, I don't know. I think it's maybe
Your chances may be improved. I never received a gift membership until after I donated memberships to a channel
Before then I had never received well now we receive like five
No, baby, that ain't that ain't the same guy
But that ain't the same guy
Because Doug B is a little wild so I was like oh
The first time I had Dougie Doug on the show that day, like Dougie was like saying,
Oh, thank you for having me on the show. It was so nice to meet you and so like anything and then he's like
I have him okay, I had please have a mod I was on the show today, and I was like, I don't know
I was like, oh my gosh, what is he and then Goddy was saying that it was him. He was like, oh, yeah, that's
That's the same guy. I was getting so confused. So, you know
Listen, 90% of the time, whatever Gotti says, it's like the opposite.
Oh, you know Gotti.
You come from the Gotti community?
No.
But I don't come from this community, and I know you, right?
So, I mean...
Hey, Amber.
I think there's just...
There are acquaintances, but I think Gotti...
Gotti comes in his chat.
Is that what people say about us is that we're like that like I'm from the site community because I hope you know us
If you stick around long enough you would be considered from
panel versus community, especially if you're a panelist that joins a lot.
There's communities, right?
Yeah, we've heard of a lot of them, but this is my main one.
You can't pretend they don't exist.
What I find hard is to like not be labeled that way,
because that is how people label, I don't like it either,
when people label me like that page,
but they do because of where I go,
and you get labeled too because of where you go.
yeah i don't mind it i don't care psychs my homie he's my boy and that changes as you
as years go by and you go different places communities that used to be part of you no
longer are and then you get new ones and and that's the way it's been i'm new here let's hear
duggy dug for you to assume page doesn't like it you know it's crazy okay she just says she
You're right that makes a lot of sense though like I mean there is communities that I used to be a part of that like
I mean some of them don't even have channels anymore or they have you know change to whatever their content is or whatever
The fuck it might be right so
But anyway, I like this community these are my people but I like
This is my home and you're part of the psych community. That's just what it is
Well, I wouldn't have met any of these cool cats if I wasn't you know
So I'm kind of feel lucky to be a part of this community. It wasn't easy to be a part of it either. You have to earn that shit
It's a wrong community
The other thing of course page is that you're not like part of just one community
You'd be part of like a dozen different communities. Yeah, it's like a web, right? You know what I mean?
Yeah, but some may I'll tell you I see him all over the place
He knows I go down by surf dogs. I go other places where I see this guy. They're all different track communities
Yeah, there's just some places I just know to stay away from so I haven't been there yet or maybe I'm not ready to
But you know I'm figuring it all out. These guys are pretty good at teaching me a lot of shit. So I've been grateful for that
Blurred a lot from them all
I talked to me last night. Oh, yeah, actually somebody or show last night for a little bit and then I
Don't remember it was really all blur
Yesterday was insane, dude. I freaking yelled at raging demon. I screamed at him like a crazy person. Oh
Really why happened page? I did hear a little bit. So I didn't I didn't catch it
It's anything that happens like after a I'm probably more than more than likely asleep if I'm not on the panel
But I heard he was a he was speaking on somebody's
You know so beacon on fucking beacon at her and I'm him and flirty or beacon at fucking beta and then
Then he's gonna be cannot psych and then I lost my shit cuz like have some what
Yeah, he started yelling at psych and then I started fucking flipping out
They started flipping out on me and then I had to leave
Somebody gotta have that love it was on be the channel
Psych was it here or was that beat us?
No, it was here. It was here. It was here
Because what happened was we came over to Surprise Rage Psyche, because we were all up
beat us for like hours, all of us girls, and then fucking we came over just to say hi
to Psyche and whatever and support and fucking Raging Demon and Flirty were up talking shit
and then so they thought we came to just talk shit, but we didn't and then it just turned
into a big fucking huge fight.
Oh, so it was the morning show, right?
Yeah.
The morning show.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I got it.
Hello, is this Paige from the from the psych verse? Yes, you're speaking to me. Oh my god. Oh my god. Yes
Paige I have some bad news for you. Why?
You always come in with the positivity no matter what is going on in your life
You always bring the positivity and you have some
But I gotta I gotta start the drama right now. I'm so sorry Paige
I'm sorry, I there will be no cursing though. I will refrain hurry up. Damn
Relaxed dude
What happened what you do if you disrespect pain you have a problem you know never that never that never that that's princess page right there
You're her princess Pocahontas right there. You're
What's going on, Arthur?
Quick no, no, it's nothing with you page. I'm just giving you the heads up that drama is on the way now towards you
No, nothing with you. Okay. Go ahead man. Go ahead. Yeah
Sike, good afternoon, where are my manners?
Aldo, good afternoon.
So that is?
Look, wait, nobody gets to say hi to me, it's the fuck?
Is that it?
Didn't you just say it?
So the only thing you had to say is she got-
Where are my manners first?
I said hi to you first, where are my manners?
First thing that first thing I did
He trolling he trolling just don't page never take this guy serious. Please never take him serious. That's it
So anyways, anyways, I wanted to acknowledge Santa Claus here
you. Um Doug, you've been, uh,
you've been talent-seeking what
to do a lot lately. Bita and I
were talking about you. You're
you're out of your mind. What's
the matter with you? I never told
anybody what to do. No, negative,
negative Santa Claus. We're not
in that. I thought he was the
first time he was up here. No,
it's definitely not the first
time this guy has been telling
He has everybody is running the way you want to
He's always saying, oh, you know, I I don't think that was a good idea leaving people on panel, you know, I think that's
Gary I mean you you from New York, man, I'm starting to think you Gary
We should probably figure something out with that by the way because last night I tried to call you like six times because the panel like you needed one of us up there at some point because you were asleep.
I don't know who you left up there but it was a lot of fucked up talk and I just like don't you need to figure out something out where you could like maybe me or Jamie or somebody that's usually like awake still are watching the channel that can kind of maybe maybe fucking assist with that because you need some help when you fall asleep.
Mm-hmm. So you took so do you don't got to manage your mind no more psyche didn't did uh
What's the name administrator for a stream yard? No
No, yeah, that's right. My bad. You're right. You're right, Arthur. Uh, you don't have a uh stream yard mod the admin
Don't give control of your shit to other
There you go. Thank you. What you do there you go. Yeah, there you go
Dougie with all due respect psyche does know some people that he can trust with like his
They'll get you around here. All right, so shut it Santa Claus
No negative feelings were hurt. Oh, what a shame
What pisses me off
Let's all feel bad for Arter shall we this is what pisses me off psyche. Yeah, he didn't even say your name, right?
He called you Arter
So this is what pisses me off us like yeah, I've heard a lot of people come here and tell you what to do fine
but he keeps bugging his channel every goddamn time after it
No, no, he does not
Yes, he does
That's ridiculous
You know, I don't agree with her
I like how to say I want to post his channel
I mean, I do and don't post his channel and please though
But yeah, what did you say just this week? You were like, I have to stop being so gullible. People have to tell me stop being gullible. Remind me to stop being so gullible. I'm trying to tell you right now, dude, this guy is constantly, you know, in my channel, you know, we got a bunch of moderators over there. They're
Arthur, you know, we can go and
I'm not worried about it.
Stop harassing Dougie.
How about when you're asking me what happens when I drop the soap in the shower?
He just makes himself look foolish when he does this.
I'm not worried about it.
Everybody can hear him.
He should be embarrassed.
You're embarrassing.
So I'm not worried about it.
Santa Claus
Don't disrespect him I'm just saying
He from New York, man, you know, listen, are you are you from Staten Island? Gary? I mean Dougie
When I was two and a half, I do not remember living in the city with the 15 miles north
of New York City.
I worked in the city as an iron worker.
It kind of looks like a scumbag.
He smells like a scumbag, and then he must be a scumbag.
Come on, Arthur, chill out.
Chill out, Arthur, chill out, man.
He's a fucking python.
Y'all can smell it.
All right, OK, man.
OK, we get it, man.
No, I'm sorry, dude, but I the minute I've been hearing this guy. Well, you know, in my channel everything is better
Yeah, I haven't heard that
He has been dude. He has even beat a cold amount
Has he been like that psyche because you know, we don't like that
You know when psyche has a new toy he'll fucking bend over backwards psyche don't psyche. He don't like old
Yeah, it's like it like younger.
Whoa.
Legal younger.
Legal.
Good save.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A hundred times if you've done your nuts and given up your complaining honor.
Our third sir, I know you might have an accent, but our third
Okay
It was purposely done that for new people. I wanted to hear them say Ardur
Yo, Santa Claus
Santa Claus, I got a couple questions
There's a couple evil people here in the community one of them being a rage and semen
Will he be receiving Paul or dildos this year?
He's gonna receive my little fist in his face. That's what he's gonna get. Oh shit. He's just threatening now
She's on her soft soft girl era page in the soft girl era
Was able to seduce fucking uh raging and shit, you know, because uh
Totally, you know, she's popping in raging to do her dirty work and shit to be honest
You know, but but it's funny because you know, that's a that's a guy. That's a man. You know, I'm just saying that's a man
Great region lost all the respect I didn't have for a man
Let's see if I can y'all hear me, yeah, you just kind of sounded like a cyborg for a
second.
It was the submarine pings, right?
Shut up Santa Claus.
You're a noble dude.
You realize that this guy is
Remember I've given you the heads up
Do you want like what do you want? I think psyche fell asleep
His favorite thing to do when he's up on
The cat I'm coming with a cat in the blanket. I'm listening. There's a fucking scumbag
Oh my god, you're lucky. I don't want I can't curse because it's okay. I won't I don't care
I just said fuck like six times. Oh, okay. Fuck you, Dougie. Fuck you piece of shit
I thought he said when he came up that he wasn't gonna do that. No, he made it quite clear that he was going to do that
Well, that's what
He said he said that's exactly what the guy in the chat said but he tells you that what he means is that's what he's gonna do
Yeah, Arthur when he says he's doing something he's really quite quite adamant about it. Yes
He's got something to say he's gonna say it
Unless you guys have a history and we don't know about it, you know what I mean
Okay, well then that's something that's that's then well, I don't know just just take it for his warning
I guess for a grain of salt and just go with the flow
Use your own discernment, but he's just looking out for you for what he's feeding from energy
And you have to respect that too, right? No offense, Dougie. Just you know, he's our boys. You've got to respect that
I'm not worried about what you mean, but that guy said I'm not. Oh, yeah. No. No, it's just in general like, you know
Just everybody in general. I completely ignore the idiots in general. That is to say I don't participate
I don't give them sadness. I may answer back a little when I'm on a panel
But when I'm in chat what I've learned when when not when you're typing to people, you know, it only if you
The best thing to do
is to like completely ignore them.
Don't block them, just ignore everything they say.
Then they sit there typing looking stupid,
looking like an idiot trying to provoke a fight, right?
I don't respond to bullshit.
Now, I did respond a little up here, but not much.
I was kind of-
Right, you've been responding, man.
You responded the whole time, Dougie Doug.
I mean, you might not do it over there,
but you've been doing it here.
You're saying well like I said I
Did respond a little bit
But I'm not gonna like start cursing at him. I'm not gonna start calling him names, you know, whatever like that bullshit
What did I tell him? I even forgot what I told I asked him how many times he did his nuts since he's been up there
But you know
So what is your platform about my platform mean about nothing?
Not about politics, not about religion,
and it's not about being unpleasant.
In fact, the opposite.
The first thing I say in my guidelines
is keep the chat pleasant.
Probably be a boring ass chat.
Yeah, I was just gonna say that I'm super pleasant
in all about positivity, but even I like a good scratch.
Like drama, I like negativity, I feed off negativity.
A lot of people who go to chat to the highly negative and where they're a bunch of bullshit come to my place and they're chill and relax and they don't fuck around.
I'm this place is chill.
Yeah, so you have so many viewers you get how many viewers you get their Dougie Doug with the positivity and all that you get good.
I get sometimes more than others, you know, I would say on average about 20.
And a good night maybe maybe 40 if it's if there's a lot of people
Very often towards the end of the night less and less, you know how that goes
Hey sassy. What's up, honey?
Okay, what's up gangster? Um, what else is going on in the chat?
Like I said, I get people who are out in chat fighting, but then they come to my place and they're really chill and they don't do that shit.
Well.
People don't fuck around at mine either, but it's also like they kind of know who I am and what to like
What I expect from them when they come to mind mind you I don't mind a little bit of banter
But like just because you can hip it in the bud right away
We can fuck around when we come over here. You know what I mean?
My channel is it's for that's why don't you like I can do stream here to have it and I'm like approved for it
I just I don't know if I should do that. I mean, I should start a different channel for that
You gotta do what you're comfortable page. Like I said to psych and like I say to everybody who streams, you know
Be true to yourself. Don't let other people tell you what to do. If you're comfortable with it, that's good
No, I'm very set to know who I am and I know that
No, I know what I said before and it's okay a little bit of fun picking on each other like that's totally fine. I
Know where you went
Where's your head psyche is that your head right there with like a cat I think that's his left knee
You're like a little pop like pop goes weasel little jack in the box
Yeah big stretch
Okay, I think somebody's back somebody backstay. Oh, he's back
Bring him back up
My wife says that she's like big stretch big stretch. Is that like a tick-tock thing? No, I don't know. It's maybe some mom thing
I just so he said it my whole life big stretch big stretch
Wow, she says that
Well, look at that we're like then
So the people out there tonight, well today, Squid Game Season 3, the final season came
out.
I don't know that people are interested in watching that.
My kid watched it.
She tried to make me watch it, but I tried to watch it and I couldn't get into it.
No?
No, not really.
Like I watched as much as I could and then I kind of just find myself like looking on
my phone or trying to want to do something else, you know?
Oh man.
I did it.
But she loves it.
She fucking loves that show.
Yeah, I think this season is the last one and I'm going to binge watch it with my wifey
Well, I miss watching I miss watching shows with my non-existent husband
What do you mean? I thought she was married. Hold on
He left you or you left him well, we split up we split up he's do another thing together
He was he was he was busy with other women man. Oh my god
Yeah
So that's been really cool. He just left and he didn't come home. So I've just been dealing with everything
I'm sorry to hear that page I didn't want the topic to go there
Like nine years is a long time but like, you know, I can't choose for somebody else what they want and that's because that's not fair
You know, so it's fine
It's gonna hurt and I'm gonna be sad for a long time, but I'm getting over it every day a little bit by little, you know
Yeah, I get it. I definitely get it. Yeah
Yeah, so
Pardon yeah, I have one kid
Yeah, she's older. She's 12 so
But she's you know, you gotta always be mindful like you know
It's hard to not be kind of selfish when it comes to your feelings and your emotions and what you're going through with something like this
But she's she's going through it too. So I have to stay strong and still be her role model
You know how to get through it. So that's a good point. Wow
Okay. Wow, very admirable
Yeah, because they come first, you know what I mean they do
Although
Yo, I heard you. Uh, you were honking the horn at me motherfucker
What?
That was you the landscaper that was in the middle of the fucking road. Oh fuck you bitch fuck you
Hey, oh Santa Claus, so are you gonna be giving region demons and call this year away?
I'm not off your fucking neck bitch. Fuck you. I called him out on his lie
He said he doesn't really entertain people like you, but he he does and now
Arthur doesn't learn this lesson, you know, at least I can tone it down, but Arthur tones it up
I don't know why he hates Doug. I mean Doug seems kind of you know, but ain't bad yet
It's a character
They have been very respectful to the panelists. Gosh, they're so rude
I'm KZ. Yes, I kicked Arthur man. He was talking shit to Dougie Doug
Was he talking to me I
And then
I don't really think you look like Santa Claus
You know, I don't even say it all
We just know
There's some guys
Oh my god, I was muted this whole time and I've been talking
Holy fuck, I hate when I do that shit
Cause I was reading the chat and I forgot I put my
Turn on my mic off
So I've just been talking to you guys and not fucking
I do that shit every time I hold the live stream
I did that shit a lot man
Trying to mark details
My god, so he man, I was talking to you. I'm sorry honey that you're going through that
We can be sad together my brain's like that every single day, and it's gonna be for a while
But we'll get through it also
Person where have you been? I've really missed you. Please don't stay away so long
We've been that person no I miss you
My smart person that makes it I just love getting roasted by first actually my favorite because it's so like comes from such a loving place
My ribs are healed so I know I saw you last night, but I meant before that
Last week in your way. Okay, so it's just one weekend. See you're such a big deal that like you go away for one weekend
And I feel like it's a year
I thought I haven't seen person in a while for a little bit. Thank you
So, okay, I was unaware that you were censoring me that you didn't want me to I
Guess well, what's the rule today? Say if you could let me know before I cross that rule
This is the world. I don't want you going that does man
I said Santa Claus though, I never said that guy does it.
I don't worry, you can say whatever he wants.
It wasn't the Santa Claus that was you saying.
It was the Santa Claus that directed you and me.
Psyche, I said Santa Claus, I don't know why you kicked me out.
I'm not saying it.
Arthur, you're gonna get like farts in your stocking or something instead of.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm gonna get like an evil eye for fucking Psyche.
You're gonna get some shit in there for sure.
Catch it by psyche
Guido
Hey, man, this sounds awesome. Hi herbs. What's up, buddy?
Hi
Can I call you Frank? Oh my god, we got Santa Claus and we got fucking Harry Potter, man
What did dr. Dre saying
Nothing you idiots dr. Dre's dead. He's locked up a basement
Sorry that was not cool, I'm not doing that. I was it was okay
That was an insider joke. I could not not say it. No one else horse. It's up Frank
What's up?
Nothing these cool cats, you know, I gotta get ready for work soon though
So I might have to hop down in like five minutes when I'm done my dart
Hey, yo, Harry Potter, what's up?
How you doing there, how you doing
The last time I bring like June summer have some kind of beef. I love like
She's like, oh, she's like she was trying to throw you off my panel, but I didn't think
No, but if you had a history or something or like why oh summer. Oh summer
Yeah
Yeah, I remember summer. I like summer man. I hope you have a wonderful rest of your day, honey
That sounds so freaking awesome all that treats and snacks and family time. You're gonna have a good one. You'll feel better
Hi lava, what's up?
I'm always mean. I'm always drunk as well, so
Well be rude not to you know, I suppose you don't have shit to do. I'm not mean I'm just Dutch
No, well that that's works, but that's like me saying I'm not an alcoholic. I'm just native
Dougie, uh, Frank has a true crime, uh, program on YouTube, so he's from another area.
I love true crime.
Okay.
Sucks.
Yeah.
I'll watch Netflix if I want to see something like that.
Why do I gotta watch fucking Harry Potter?
He doesn't really look like Harry Potter, but he doesn't have glasses on.
He looks kinda like...
I mean
He looks like we all know who he looks like he looks like two fucking people he looks like the guy from up and he looks like
Oh, okay
Now that was Harry Potter now. No break is great. Wait, which guy from up the old guy
Wait, who looks like him Dougie. Oh, no, don't assault my
The guy the guy from what the movie up the kids movie up you Dougie
Can you put a picture show a picture put it up under a thing find a picture somebody
Don't insult my movie like that. I love that movie. Come on. There's also a movie down. Well, I guess it's not really movies more documentary
For children like
Never mind
Well, I didn't you didn't I didn't say you said it. I said it Frank. What verse do you come from?
Yeah
Frank a verse what a true crime verse the truth. Well go back nobody wants you here
I think that Arthur's being rather PG today.
I mean, look, Psyche, and I'm always going to bring this up to you.
You were a big fan of Howard Stern, right?
You always love that shock, jock radio.
I'm here for it. I'm here to push the buttons.
But you, you're like, you're always censoring me.
I don't get it. You're like, no, that's not TOS appropriate.
And then the next minute, you're going to ask me, hey,
when we're sharing together and I dropped the soap.
What's gonna happen next?
That's not TOS appropriate.
I've never said that, dude.
You never said that!
I
Okay
Thank you, dude, drink sometimes and say some stuff
What happens if we both think a shower and
Break is here, so I'm not interested in anybody else. Yeah, exactly
No, no, no. I mean, I mean, I'm just saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm
Okay, you're welcome. You're welcome guys. There's got to be quite a ruckus in another community. Oh, why?
Are you talking some ruckus in some other community, um, right?
What are you causing a ruckus in some other community? It's low. Um, a globe. He says
Yeah
What are you hiding because we'll find out
You're gonna read about it all already people bitch all the time, but you know
Yeah, exactly
They still do that that is mostly in courtrooms though
That's it. I thought there was when they were spreading news on the streets as well. And I was not here you hear you. Oh, what was it?
Here you hear you is mostly in courtrooms
Isn't it just listen here listen here in a sense so then you could say that on the streets to just fine
Whatever flip you both I only heard it
Well, I okay. Well, that's fair, but like otherwise I want to hear what you what do you what do they do with when they do that help me out
Chas am I wrong? It's totally cool if I'm wrong. I
Don't know if you're a town crier a town crier. Okay
Who's our town crier
See the thing is is that people don't like me and it's fine, but they can't let it fucking loose
And so they need to fucking rehash it because there are a bunch of insecure little pussies
So that is what is I cover true crime. I don't fucking cover comedy. I don't cover
Fucking the rose petals. I cover real shit, and you know if I people they're feeling so be it
But I come here to remind us so
It's like why do you always need to keep saying that I have a true crime channel?
So right, you know, oh, it's all right. I'm sorry. I thought you did. I'm sorry. No, buddy. How do you describe it?
I'm not I'm not saying that you are not covering facts, but just because I come on I don't mean necessarily your shot
Oh, yeah, no, well, I like I mean I wish I like for more other people. That's what I do. They're just a habit. So
Yeah, yeah, you can promote everyone. So, um, yeah
Let's see Spanish whoopies. I don't I'm very confused too. Oh
Everyone's everyone's here. Oh, there you go
Hey, let's hatch works
Probably with tricks of the blanket
It's how you do it like I'm okay
I don't know. Okay. It's uh it's
a good Friday. Yeah, I'm
having a great Friday. Uh I'm
just ready for the weekend.
You know, I uh it's only it's
only 1251 here so I don't know.
Maybe I'll you know, I'm always
excited to get to like the
evening time so I can start
party. Have you started party
yet or is it too early for you?
I always party because there
ain't no party like an
alcoholic party.
Well, I got I have you vapes, you know, I got you know, I've been sort of these vapes and they're very powerful
Vapes or dates?
Vapes. It's like a vape. It's like this thing right here. See
Straighten mile high. It's a you know
Awesome
I'm sure you've sure you've seen them here his face back here
Is that a penjaman or a douche flute?
Like like a tobacco vape is a douche flute pen, you know weed pens a penjaman, which one is it?
Anyways, I have like ten minutes and then I gotta go shower and get ready for work cats
What do you do for work page I work at a golf course and I do absolutely everything there from kitchen stuff to fucking
Maintenance to fucking golf cart caddy to flicker to serving to anything in the world that you'd they need me to do
I do
Do you wear those clashing forts?
Well, I'm a golfer myself, so I definitely have some attire, some classy attire, but I
don't have to wear it's pretty casual.
I can wear whatever the fuck I want, because I'm kind of up there.
You play golf, Paige?
Yeah, I do, actually.
I take it very seriously.
So, you work there, you get to play there, and you work there, and it's all good to get
paid.
Yeah, I can do whatever. Yeah, I make tips. I can play golf whenever I want. I can do whatever I want
I can go there after hours and play golf. I can stay later. I can do whatever I want drink at the clubhouse and stope
Sounds like a good job
It is a great job. Yeah, but I think they're gonna sell it this year
But my friend wants to buy it and then he wants me to go in
And like as a business partner and help him with some stuff
So I think that might be cool and might be able to make it work because there's a campground there too, right?
So it's a bit of everything and then he wants to open a safety shop. So
Okay, your friend wants to buy the golf club where you work. Yeah, because they're putting it up for sale
So the people you do what buying is a partner or do just have a have a small share
Just a small sharing to help them establish like to help
There could be good money in that. No, there is gonna be good money. It's a good. It's an excellent business opportunity
I'm definitely looking into it. Yeah, that's what I'm saying golfers. You know, if you're gonna play golf
It's not because you're poor, right? It's
So I think
I think that there's probably a very good market there.
Around here, around here where I am,
we have golf courses all over the place
and they're always full.
People I know that play golf,
they're like, I can't get a tee time
until two weeks or whatever, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
No, it's great and I already know how to do everything there, right?
So like what they'd be doing is just handing over the business as is when they sell it because my friends own it and then
So if my other friend buys it, then it's just like I already know what the big it's already like established everything's established
It just has so much potential
It just needs upgrades and then you can do whatever you want with it plus grow
And there's also like a modular home and another home attached, like a house attached to the
clubhouse that was my friend's mom's but she's in the hospital so she's not living there anymore.
So there's, but then there's actually like rental properties on the place as well or you can live there as well.
Rental income opportunity. And now, do you, do you sell like annual membership? So is it like public first come first serve?
No, it's, it's, it's, it's all of it. So you have, you can have your memberships and there's leaves.
Okay. And then there's also, you know, just the public can come in as well.
So members get priority when it comes time to play, right?
Yeah, absolutely, of course they do but they also have certain nights that are dedicated like certain days that they have
They come in and they get specialties and and they get to do their own thing and have their own freedom as well
Yeah
Any other amenities in the club besides golf you have like I don't know weight rooms
There's a storage unit. There's storage units. There is the campground
There is the Cooper's pit, which is kind of somewhere you can go fishing and swimming
It's right by the river like this. Let's so it's very very very very profitable
Like in the sense of if you're going to be you know looking into buying something like that
There's no way that you can fail sounds like a good opportunity. Yeah, yeah, and it's been here forever
It's one of the like oldest, you know
it's an older one so it's been around this place for a long time and people come from like big
cities around here just just because they've had a great experience it's for the experience right
and it's actually not an easy course it's a little bit more laid back it's not super like
swanky but it definitely um it's a hard course like I've had it's one of the harder courses I've
Cool. Yeah. So yeah, anyways, that's what I do. And then I'm also an artist and a mom and I'm gonna go to school
And I think in the wintertime and take some upgrading with my medical career or I'm gonna go and do realtor
License or something like that. I don't know. You said real estate. Mm-hmm
But there's like
If you're gonna be trying to run a golf course business might be a good
Well, yeah, no, of course, but I already have it. I already have a business
Yeah, so I've already done that yet
Okay. Yeah
Well very cool page. Yeah, I just thought the realtor course would be six like eventually one day flip houses
You know what I mean? There's a lot of revenue in that
What are they really to get six percent per sale or something right?
Uh, yeah. Thanks, dog.
Oh, the cat just attacked my kid.
Are you okay, Grace?
Sorry.
Oh, my cat just attacked my kid's leg.
Your cat's attacking you, huh?
Well, she just, like, was playing with a string on Grace's pants.
She didn't mean to.
She wasn't, like, attacking her aggressively.
She was just playing.
Yeah, all right. Well fucking what are you guys doing with the rest of your day? You're just gonna hang out
I'm not gonna be late for work, and if I am they're not gonna say nothing cuz I'm always early
Okay, but if you're not if you're not early or late, right?
If you're not early or late, yeah, yeah, if you're not first you're last. I'm just kidding. We're not gonna be late
And we have to do my hair
Actually live like near it too, so it's not bad just a little cut across a couple gravel roads over and I'm at work
Yeah, we're like we're like 30 minutes from everything Grace you live in the middle of fucking nowhere
How's it's had you in grace color fits like terrible get it because little headphones is
Seattle
No, she's not going to say hi to you. She waved but she's like my she don't give a shit
It's too weird, it looks like a wig, or Onision, or is that guy's name Onision?
Now you're sleeping, you're sleeping under there, right Sike?
Am I sleeping right now?
No, when you were under the blanket you were asleep.
Oh, no I'm just totally with my cat, I'm just with a cat like a total.
He just likes to watch the back of his eyelids and count feet for a little break.
And I like sort of the hip-hop and then it's like I get the kind of like you're kind of like I like to meditate for a second
But there's a way where Julia. I know
You'll get these years away
Yeah, but I'm awake now. I'm not gonna leave anybody
I do trust the dog of course and uh, which my hair grew as fast as your fucking hair. It's like
Yeah, there's all the hair on my body grows. I like, you know what I mean?
It's just a woman thing though because we have to shave things right and that's like
If my hair if I even trim it and I'm like, oh, no, I can't wait for it to grow back
You know what it takes like 85 fucking years like I'll be a skeleton before I even get it past like for like two inches
And then am I fucking leg hair and like just woman Harry that we remove is like oh you shaved me
I better grow back in one second the instant you get cold you can feel your hair grow back
It's not worth the same for your head
The women in the chat will totally know what I mean pages Harry. You know that person
Not right now though because after like, you know, it's summertime. So it's a wintertime thing
That Canadian girl fucking
shag
It's your pictures is pictures into a sasquatch every winter every winter. Yeah, just a total yeti like
Okay, love you guys
Okay, I'll talk to you on my break bitches. Bye. Bye
Bye
Yeah, look yeah page is one of the
Bright lights of the show, you know
You know page up on your panel a bunch. She was up a long time
Maybe it was yesterday. Mm-hmm. Yeah, there's a lot of people that
Like you know to make their debut on the show on the first panel a lot of people will go on and then I don't know like some people
Yeah, you know the page is a great front. Yeah
And plus Paige really does fit in with the theme of the show because she's a reader as well.
And I do know a lot of great talented readers. I love having different readers up here
so people can, an audience can experience different kinds of readings.
I give one kind of reading and people, everyone has different styles.
It's also, it's just a fun, a variety of show that people showcase especially in the business, I know.
But I know, yeah, last night I had a bobby rave it up and then it was fun
And then like but I kept bringing back this woman destiny and this woman was very drunk and this like and then she was getting
She started getting like, you know
I don't know, I don't know, I
don't know, I don't know, I
Maybe a bagel at the bagel store, you know the close of 130 a thing
Okay
Okay, the four o'clock we'll have a wonderful day
Anytime thank you
Thanks so much
Yep
So yeah, it's great having some good friends of the show, you know, and that's why I try to
Kind of keep it a little bit more
Respectful, but I
Don't know I just want to sure would
Have it a good time. You're welcome. Dougie Doug. Thank you. Great. We're having on the show. Hey, Dougie. That's a nice guy
I heard she was trying to seduce Page, who was, someone was trying to seduce Page?
I can find my phone.
Oh, yeah, she was destiny was
That was I mean that was funny that there were funny parts and then then she would like she was so unpredictable though
She then she would go to like oh
Something to talk about like the United States and stuff like
Is the video still up? I'm not sure, Jamie. I'm sorry.
I don't know if you have members only.
Not the video where I fell asleep, the one before that, I'm not sure.
I sometimes put them on members only sometimes. If they're too bad, I'll just leave them.
Hey, Instacarma!
Thank you so much. Oh, I love you
Wishing you a wonderful day, but actually make great life only good karma a little
Just limit a little safety. Oh, thank you so much. It is so nice of you
Awesome, thank you so much
Do you have your bagel a copy cover today? Yeah, I think I'm gonna get they have this
They have a
Special it's had it has locks and stuff on it. I liked I had it before
And it has like a hash brown and I think it has a muffin a muffin too, but I don't know if I ate the muffin
Hungry for it
No, I seem to find my
Think it's about you see that's whole bucks
Yeah, I
Think it again, yeah, I gotta
Thank you so much Insta-carbo
You see I'm gonna look at my app
I keep losing my phone
It is about to close, so I'm not getting any of you to hurry.
Ahhhh!
I mean, I haven't even gotten up so how can I find anything?
What happened here?
I'm just a mess right now.
Okay, well, I can go order it.
I need to have the phone to go over there, too.
I just had it.
Oh, I found it, okay.
Yay.
I can order it from the app.
It's Einstein bagels, yeah, Einstein Brothers bagels.
We're now, yeah.
It's, continue to walk in.
You're in there to see. Oh, I love you
It's a karma. I hope to see you soon love you so much. Thank you so much again
I just get a just a pizza bagel
Oh, pizza bagel. That's brownie pizza bagel.
Did the check of the hobo, but there's a betraying. Okay. Well, let's walk over there. I'll just put it on my have 20 minutes to get there
so
No, let's get it there
Mm-hmm.